{
    "id": "5ceee34b7a0c4d35b71bdf29578ba090",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I like to hang ……………………… with my friends in the evening.",
            "description": "To hang out is to spend time relaxing and enjoying yourself.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bf6e55f6abde47e98ff3326552813b47"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before I could say anything she hung …………………….",
            "description": "To hang up is to end a telephone conversation by cutting the connection.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f88445950b99450a9d1f4d8b39388567"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hang ………………………. ! I am coming.",
            "description": "To hang on is to wait for a short time.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98e4a88d139a43cba16cb0daa36fa1de"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a cut ……………………….. the rest.",
            "description": "When you are a cut above the rest, you are better than others.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d47d2491488438cb87a1c8145c2d40d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is cut ……………………….. for the show business.",
            "description": "If you are cut out for something, you have the right qualities for it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d147f0fd58c9473cadd2c8359b84e41a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will reach faster if we cut ……………………….. the meadow.",
            "description": "To cut across something is to go through it. ",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "across",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a8727f81d1948209d8bbb430f798e73"
        },
        {
            "question": "You always cut ……………………… when we are discussing something serious.",
            "description": "To cut in is to interrupt someone.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "652d6d4ec33749ea82ebeb43dbaca6aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looked cut ……………………. so I asked what the matter was.",
            "description": "Cut up means very upset.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79a2b4b3e2a84c14a8a4a7fd51880ecc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like it when you run me ……………………… in front of my colleagues.",
            "description": "To run somebody down is to criticize them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2128b9f7d86a4119b52e78a1600ae0ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let me run ………………………… the details of the program again.",
            "description": "To run through is to go over as a quick rehearsal.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "in",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d27e55f82fab434ba0c3d8971c25975f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many top level athletes have pulled ………………………… of the event.",
            "description": "To pull out is to withdraw.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "78b439893185459aa33891f8bbecbf1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She can pull ……………………… any outfit.",
            "description": "To pull off is to succeed in doing something difficult.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a92ff9b40ed4b8ba353f3f26f2b44cb"
        }
    ]
}